(Sheldon:)May I point out to you all
(Sheldon:)that the screening is
"first come, first served"?
Relax, it's 5:00. The movie
doesn't start till midnight.
(Sheldon:)Another way of saying that is
"the movie starts at midnight,
and it's already 5:00."
(Sheldon:)Let's go.
(Howard:)You know, if we miss it,
we'll have the fun of
(Howard:)listening to Sheldon whine about
it for the rest of our lives.
(Sheldon:)See? Howard's on my side.
(Howard:)Actually, I'm not.
(Howard:)I'm using sarcasm to mock you.
(Sheldon:)Drat. Now I'm 8 for 27.
(Leonard:)Don't worry, Sheldon.
We'll be fine.
What happened to
the Leonard Hofstadter
who waited in line
with me for 14 hours
to see the midnight premiere
of Star Trek: Nemesis?
Oh. Well, he waited
in line for 14 hours,
while you napped
in a lawn chair,
he got in a fight
with a Klingon
when he stepped
out of line to pee
and you wouldn't wake up
to vouch for him,
and worst of all,
he saw Star Trek: Nemesis.
(Sheldon:)But how were our seats?
(Leonard:)Excellent.
(Sheldon:)I rest my case.